there's a real danger that telsy Gabbert
is not going to be confirmed and it's
not because the Democrats are United
against her the Democrats are United
against her it's that she's having
trouble keeping the Republicans United
because this whole Maga thing is already
beginning to wear thin among some
Republican Senators and where Tulsi is
really getting tripped up is section 702
of the fisa ACT uh you know Tulsi is of
the same mind that we are when it comes
to warrantless surveillance it's wrong
it should be illegal it should be
unconstitutional and somehow the
government keeps getting away with it
every two years when it's when it's
reapproved by uh the the house and the
Senate she has had to tell Senators
Republican senators in these private
meetings that she's been having the last
several weeks that she supports renewal
of 702 we know that she doesn't support
renewal of 702 now I'm hoping that she's
saying that because she knows she has to
say it to win their votes and get
confirmed I hope then that she can have
an epiphany or a revelation once she's
the Director of National Intelligence
and she can back out of that that would
be a very Washington thing to do